<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mae Milano</title>
    <link>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mae Milano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for new PhD students!</title>
      <link>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/looking-for-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/looking-for-students/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m actively looking for new PhD students! Hey! If you&amp;rsquo;ve found this page, you&amp;rsquo;re (hopefully) looking at me as a potential advisor for a PhD in computer science. Welcome! I&amp;rsquo;m starting at Princeton for next semester (officially January 17th 2024), which makes fall 2023 the perfect time to apply to the PhD program!
What might we work on together? My research focuses on designing new Programming Languages to solve problems in Distributed Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dissertation is Now Available!</title>
      <link>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/dissertation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/dissertation/</guid>
      <description>After many years at Cornell University, I have finally completed my PhD journey! My dissertation, entitled &amp;ldquo;Programming Safely with Weak (And Strong) Consistency&amp;rdquo;, is now available via ProQuest (or directly from me).
That document is 364 pages, is there a summary? Sure! The unifying theme of my dissertation is that writing programs against weak consistency is inherently difficult. My dissertation makes the job of writing safe programs against weak consistency easier, by introducing programming languages in which strong guarantees are defended from weakly-consistent influence, and in which programmers can write consistent-by-construction programs atop underlying weakly-consistent replication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixing Consistency with MixT: Technical Report Available!</title>
      <link>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/mixt-tr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://languagesforsyste.ms/post/mixt-tr/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long wait. It was our great pleasure to present the MixT paper at this year&amp;rsquo;s PLDI, but we always felt that the conference version was missing a few details and extra explanations which (we sincerely hope) would go a long way towards explaining the MixT approach to distributed transactions. So it makes us overjoyed to finally make the extended Technical Report of the MixT paper available to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>